ssnet.org 2018-12-28

# Sabbath School Net Privacy Policy – Sabbath School Net

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [Sabbath School Net](http://ssnet.org/). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

### Information We Routinely Collect

We collect your email address when you submit a comment to us. We expect this to be a workable email address if you expect us to publish your comment. 

### **Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you or in your public comments on our site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We may use your email address to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, unless you request this. 

We do not store your email address apart from the comments you submit or the email message(s) you send to us. And your email address is visible only to site administrators and moderators. Visitors will never see your email address, unless you include it in the body of your comment(s), and we strongly discourage that. (In fact, we usually delete personal contact information in comments.)

We may contact you via email in the future to tell you how to ensure that your comments are more valuable or to tell you why your comments were not published. 

### What We Do Not Collect

When you click on some of our links to purchase items, you will be directed to another site such as [Amazon.com](http://amzn.to/2cYpBpi) or [ChristianBook.com](http://www.christianbook.com/Christian/Books/home?event=AFF&amp;p=1181722). We will not know what you buy or how you pay for your purchase, etc. All this information is securely kept by the merchant from whom you buy a product. While we can see _what_ people have bought by clicking through our links, we can not tell _who_ bought these products. 

### **Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. Your email address is not visible to anyone but our moderators. 

The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information (your email address) are kept in a secure environment.

### **Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via our[Contact Us form](http://ssnet.org/about-us/fscontact-admi/).**

Amen!(1)
